https://www.headfortgolfclub.ie/privacy-statement/

Home » Privacy Statement Privacy Statement
At Headfort Golf Club we take your privacy very seriously. We will only use your personal
information to administer your account and to provide the products and services you have
requested from us.
What information do we collect about you?
When you join or visit our Club we collect only information required from you to be able to
fulfil our contractual obligations. We may also collect further information through our
website which allows us to contact you regarding events and offers at the Club.
As an employee we collect only the information required to fulfil the contractual
relationship between you and the Club and we only share this information with internal and
external data processors.
For security purposes CCTV is in operation both within the Clubhouse and external environs
of the Club.
How the information about you will be used
We use information provided for the following purposes:
To operate the Club and provide golfers with booking, event management and other
services they request.
For internal club record keeping.
To send informative or promotional emails that we deem of interest, with the option
to opt out from receiving these types of communications at any time. We do not
share your data with external marketing companies who would contact you in this
way.
When you join as a member or book a tee time as a visitor we may share your information
with external and internal data processors such as our membership administration system
or tee time booking service provider. Your personal data is controlled internally by the
Club’s Data Protection Officer who adheres to the Club’s internal data protection policies
and procedures and has been satisfied by the privacy policy of all external data processors.
Otherwise, Headfort Golf Club will not share your personal information without consent
except where the Club has a legal obligation to disclose the information (such as responding
to a court order), to protect the Club’s legal rights or to prevent fraud or illegal activity.
Individual rights
You have the right to request a copy of the information we hold about you. If you would like
a copy of this information please email us or write to the Data Controller at the Club. This
will be provided to you in a portable, machine readable commonly used format.
We want to make sure that your personal information is accurate and up to date so you may
ask us to correct or erase information that you think is inaccurate.
At the time of collecting data you have the right to object to the Club holding certain
information about you.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
We keep our privacy policy under regular review and place any updates on our website. This
privacy policy was last updated on 17th May 2018.
How to contact us
If you need further information please email info@headfortgolfclub or write to us at:
Headfort Golf Club
Navan Road
Kells
Co. Meath.
Ireland
Thank You to all our sponsors who generously support the activities and contribute to the Headfort Golf Club
Headfort Golf Club aspires to the highest standards of excellence in the playing of the game of golf for both members and visitors
By providing two very different 18 Hole golf courses Headfort Golf Club provides a unique golf experience
Send an email
Club Pro Shop:
+353 (0)46 9240639
Club Restaurant:
Contact Us
Created by Flo Web Design.
×
Please wait while we validate your login
LOGIN
Note: We have recently changed our site, however, the GUI numbers and passwords used on the old site remain the same.If you do not know your password you can recover it here
Wrong username (GUI) / email or password
Username (GUI) or Email
This field is mandatory
Password
This field is mandatory
Remember me
This field is mandatory
Login
